I'm messed up in the head.
No one at this junior high realizes
how the peaceful equilibrium of daily life
teeters on the edge.
That's hilarious.
That's not...
Don't knock it until you try it, man.
Maybe I'll give it a little old tug or two.
Wonder if it'll fit.
But man, what I'd get for a big tip job.
No, stop thinking about it.
I'm a bloodthirsty beast.
When will the day come?
When will I overcome these urges?
There's the girl I want to kill most of all.
Ana Yamada.
The prettiest girl in school.
And a magazine model, apparently.
But I don't give a damn.
All I want is to see that beautiful face writhing with pain.
I can hardly control myself.
Goddamn bitch!
I'll make you regret ever looking down on me like that!
You know what?
I bet she'll look just as beautiful as a corpse.
Her body will belong to her killer.
Yes!
It will be all mine!
Every night, I think the same thing.
And hate myself for it.
Yes!
I'm really messed up in the head.
Imagine getting your face smacked with those knockers...
The classroom gets especially loud and unbearable during lunch.
But this place...
It's much quieter.
It's the one place I feel at ease.
Why are you crying?
What the heck?
What is she saying?
Uh...
Um...
Oh!
Yeah!
Sure thing.
Thank goodness.
For what?
What did she say?
What the heck is she even doing here in the first place?
Wait.
Hang on now.
Is this my chance to kill her?
Ugh.
No.
Now's not the time.
I should observe her.
Huh?
What?
We just had lunch!
Isn't that a party-sized bag?
Why is she smiling like that by herself?
Wait.
And what was with that rice ball?
Huh?
Her humming is getting more and more...
A-blank!
What the hell?
What's with this girl?
Chill out, man.
Just think about how you'll offer.
Huh?
Is she working on our social studies presentation?
All right.
Huh?
She's not using a pencil first?
Ah.
See?
You ran out of space!
Uh...
Mm-hmm.
What do you mean, mm-hmm?
Huh?
Where's my box cutter?
I've got mine.
But wait a minute.
Here.
You can use mine.
Why are you carrying it around with you?
Creepy.
If she pulls that,
then it'll be time for my big murder spectacular!
You can use this if you want.
You cut my workload in half!
Oh, that wasn't an intentional pun.
Huh?
Also, thank you!
Uh...
At least she wasn't creeped out.
The hell?
Forget about that!
Yamada...
Is using my box cutter!
Uh...
My box cutter!
That's mine!
Yamada, where have you been?
I bet you were sneaking in snacks!
Huh?
No I wasn't.
Oh...
Uh...
Here you go!
She's giving me her leftovers?
Oh, I'm not done yet.
That's fine.
Hey, don't make people do that.
I wasn't.
No, just when I was starting my murder countdown.
It's been a full day since then.
My box cutter is still in her pencil case.
My sharp tool is in her.
Of course.
It's still warm.
Don't tell me.
Did she have it gripped in her hand the whole way here?
So she wouldn't forget?
No.
Maybe she's just trying not to give me any chance to finish her off.
Wait.
She knows which desk is mine.
Really?
Okay.
Today you all will be giving your group presentations.
Huh?
Oh.
This isn't the poster I made yesterday.
Oh, that thing?
It was a total mess.
So I went and redid the whole thing.
What?
You bitch.
How could you?
She worked so hard in that poster.
Yeah, I didn't really have much time.
Girls, disgust me.
They can't even hide how horrendously envious they get.
They need one prettier than them.
I mean, girl, come on.
I can hardly believe you tried to use this chocolate smudge as part of the title.
That is pretty terrible, I guess.
See what I mean?
Yeah.
Chocolate?
Seriously?
You're always so sloppy that even you have to...
Doesn't really look like she cares, though.
For our presentation, we researched political party systems.
This is so boring.
First, we looked at the U.S. as two-party system.
Democrat and Republican.
Huh?
She's got no life left in her!
That bit earlier must have hurt her feelings!
So, basically, I think we should adopt the two-party system, too!
I really do!
Shut your face!
Our presentation will show our research into SDGs.
I wrote out our poster, so I'll let them handle the rest.
Are you all familiar with the SDGs by any chance?
SDG stands for Sustainable Development Goals.
It's an international guideline meant to create a better and more sustainable world by 2030.
Got their start in 2000.
The United Nations.
This dumb thing bothered her that much!
And the Millennium Development Goals.
No.
Shh.
Maybe in her eyes, it meant a whole lot more.
It is made up of 17 goals and 169 seconds.
A copter?
Think something happened?
Look at them all.
Think there was some sort of actor?
Stop it!
Quit looking towards Yamada while she's crying, you asshats!
I need to distract them somehow!
And that concludes our presentation.
What the heck are you doing?
Well, we're done with it.
Who cares?
That's so weird.
Yes.
Go on, then.
I messed up in the head anyway.
Now she can cry all she wants.
Hey, that's a weird-looking helicopter.
You think it's an osprey?
I know.
What the heck?
Did you check out this month's volume of CL?
Not yet.
We need to switch places, you giant!
They're so heavy!
Shut your mouth!
Or I'll kick your ass.
This a moe anime?
You know, girls who touch each other got sex on the mind.
Huh?
Right.
Just imagine Kobayashi as her boyfriend for a second.
Freaking hot, right?
Quit being such a genius of a creep!
Wish a girl like Yamada could be my friends with benefits.
I'm gonna murder you, you pig!
I'm not really into girls that are overly pretty.
Huh?
This guy's into ugly girls?
Then who's your type in this class?
S-someone like Hara, maybe?
You're a real perv, dude.
Is your brain in your dick?
What the hell?!
There she is again.
Hara!
Huh?
Are you here to read a book?
No, I'm meeting someone.
Want some?
No, I'm on a diet, but thank you.
Oh.
Yeah, I'm on one too.
Liar.
I eat what I want, when I want.
That's just my lifestyle, you know what I mean?
Talk about saying something stupid like it's smart.
Mm-hmm.
Me too.
But unfortunately, I somehow wound up looking like this.
Don't leave her hanging!
Say something!
Huh?
Kanzuki?
Oh!
You're here already.
Yeah.
Uh, so, why did you want to see me?
Huh?
You're kidding me!
Is he about to ask her out?
Well, um, you see?
Yeah.
Kind of strange seeing you two together.
You're screwing this up, Yamada!
Oh, Hara!
They say fiber is really good if you're on a diet.
Uh, um...
You're on a diet?
I'm trying to lose weight.
Uh, I think girls are better with a little extra weight.
Guys have a totally different concept of what little means.
Yeah.
No, but for me, the fatter the better is the way to go.
I'm talking a hundred kilos or more.
Ugh.
All squishy and layered.
And juicy.
Okay?
Cut it out!
Quit telling Yamada about your pervy fetish!
Pretty rude of you to only figure this out now!
But you know what you gotta do now, right?
Go on then.
Get out of there and leave them alone!
Uh, is someone here?
Maybe it was a cat!
No one's gonna believe a cat's in here!
Is she trying to tell me to act like a cat?
Meow!
I wish I was dead.
I'll take a look back there.
A realistic meow isn't gonna cut it!
That's what they sound like when they fight.
Seriously?
Mm-hmm.
That was a different cat, too.
They might get into a fight.
Uh-huh.
Meow.
You're into cats?
Yeah, I have two of my own.
Wow, seriously?
Well, we did it.
Like you did a damn thing.
Glad that worked.
Yeah.
Bye.
Uh-
What am I doing helping out the enemy?
Ana Yamada, what's that girl's deal?
Why are we always crossing paths?
She said she was in this month's volume, didn't she?
Definitely can't go in there dressed like this.
Thank you for shopping with us.
She said it was in CL, right?
This must be it.
Yamada?
No, it can't be.
Oh, they have it.
I've been hooked on this magazine lately.
Oh, really?
What's all in it?
Doesn't this cover look so pretty?
Yep, that's definitely her.
Is she seriously hoping to get noticed?
Ooh, yeah.
Don't make eye contact!
Way to lose the readers you needed.
What?
Cut that out!
You're messing with the whole store now!
Put standing ready to give out signatures!
You're not even an author!
See?
Right back where it should be.
She's got a pretty cringeworthy side to her, too, huh?
F-fine.
Guess I'll just have to buy it to make up for the girl she scared off.
Let's see then.
Ooh!
What the hell am I looking at?
I'm not seeing her in here.
There she is.
She looks like a complete stranger.
I don't even give a damn anymore.
What was I even so worked up about, anyway?
I mean...
Me and Yamada...
I've always been worlds apart.
No!
You're fine!
I don't give a damn about anything anymore.
I don't give a damn, too.
Look how you don't...
Yeah.
I see.
We only see you.
sleep last night why the hell does I have to buy that crap huh huh is that her boyfriend I mean it
figures of course she has one yeah that's just the way the world works like I even care whatever
it's called line what even is that huh really you don't use it look here see I'm how are you Nanjo
oh is he trying to pick her up you use social media oh show me dear seriously you can't play
that dumb that's funny so how do you keep in touch with all your friends then we can read
each other's minds by tuning our brains to the same wavelength what he is oh she's trying to
weird him out oh yeah can you read what's on my mind right now this guy's determined you want ice
cream more like you do nice try but I was actually thinking how much cuter you look up close what a
creep she's just not into you dude surprisingly you're pretty funny you know exactly huh are you
kidding me that's what she was waiting for that whole what is line bit so many times I've got it down to
a complete science practically but seriously what is it you know you really are adorably funny
oh come on quit looking like you enjoy it hey add me online for real sorry I
seriously though I
okay
not like it matters
who cares
I don't right
am I really messed up in the head
oh
Oh
Yamada!
Did you see? Ichikawa just sent his own bike flying.
She saw that?
Why'd you do that?
I didn't... I, um...
Well, uh...
I accidentally hit the gas. And not the brakes.
Um...
You're pretty funny, Ichikawa.
They should wait to see me once.
I had no idea to change it.
They would be so happy.
I might wait home while it sees me.
In the first place I found out too many years ago,
they haven't even had enough resources.
So, if I'm ready, I should leave.
You
頬色に 茜れ射す日は 柔らかに弾けた
斜陽に 僕らは 目も開かぬまま
I'm not happy to do anything, but I'm not happy to do anything.
I'm going to go down like this.
Thank you.
僕らは目も分かぬまま